Brad West

brad@bradonomics.com

OVERVIEW

For years I have specialized in JAMstack web development. Primarily building with Jekyll and hosting with CloudCannon

Last year I started working through The Pragmatic Studio's Ruby and Rails courses. After that I decided I'd build an Instapaper clone called Portholes, which you can view on GitHub: github.com/bradonomics/portholes

EXPERIENCE

July 2021 - Present

Team member supporting the Health Resources and Services Administration's Telehealth website: telehealth.hhs.gov

July 2020 - February 2021

I worked as the primary Jekyll developer. My responsibilities included things like:

- Building array structures for the CloudCannon platform
- Creating Ruby Gem themes to separate concerns and improve site build times
- Built Ruby script to scrape data from old website
- Frontend tasks such as building a guided website walkthrough using ShepherdJS

Web Developer — Remote — *Travel Tripper*

July 2017 - January 2019

I worked as part of a remote team building Jekyll and WordPress sites. I did a bit of documentation writing and a bit of bash scripting when necessary. I

traveled to India to help team members with build tools, train junior developers, etc.

A few highlights:

- Built and maintained WCAG/ADA compliant websites
- Used Angular to display API data from booking engine
- I was also the resident Linux admin and wrote bash scripts for the rest of the team

Web Developer — Chiang Mai, Thailand — *Iglu*

March 2014 - March 2016

I worked with a designer to build custom websites for company clients. Most were converted from PSD and built on WordPress.

EDUCATION

Payap University — Chiang Mai, Thailand

2009 - 2011, 2013 - 2014

Computer Information Systems, Communications, Hospitality Management

Ramkhamhaeng University — Bangkok, Thailand

2011 - 2012

Mass Communications